胡安，胡安怎么会是胡安？
Huan, how could it be Huan?
嘿，过来了。
Hey, here it comes.
刺客全是皇家的人。马费纳，马费纳，马费纳，马费纳。不要，就是马费纳，马费纳就是活靶子。
The assassins are all from the Royal Family. Mafena, Mafena, Mafena, Mafena. No, I mean Mafena. Mafena is a sitting duck.
县长大人，绑架豪绅，祸害县城百姓。
Your Honor, he kidnapped a wealthy magistrate and brought disaster upon the people of the county.
就是你黄老爷家的。
It's from your Master Huang's family.
我说你为什么不出钱剿匪？原来你是贼喊捉贼啊！
I was wondering why you wouldn't pay to suppress the bandits. So you're the thief crying 'Stop thief!'!
你拿枪指着我。
You're pointing a gun at me.
你想跟我火并？
You want to kill me?
你们看到了没有？这就是当麻匪的下场，就算是我亲爹也得死。死有应得。
Do you see? This is what happens when you're a bandit. Even my own father would have to die. He died a worthy death.
造反！
Rebellion!
马匪胡安又让黄老爷枪毙了五回，大义灭亲，杀人灭口，连累老身。
The bandit, Huan, was executed by Master Huang five times. He killed his own kin, silenced witnesses, and implicated this old woman.
杀人灭口，你就是马匪的头子，张麻子。
To kill to silence the witness. So you're the leader of the bandits, Zhang Mazi.
要是大义灭亲，那好吧。
If you're going to kill your own kin for the sake of justice, then fine.
你出钱，我交税。好啊！
You pay the money, I'll pay the tax. Great!
三天之后，
Three days later,
一定给县长。
It must be given to the county magistrate.
一个惊喜。
A surprise.
汤师爷，他是胡万的恩人，现在又成了你的恩人。
Master Tang, he was Hu Wan's savior, and now he's your savior as well.
你给翻译翻译。
You, explain it to me.
什么叫惊喜？
What's a surprise?
翻译翻译，什么叫惊喜？这还用翻译？
Let me translate for you. What's a 'surprise'? Does that even need translating?
我让你翻译给我听，什么叫“你”？
I asked you to translate for me. What do you mean by "you"?
惊喜！不用翻译就是惊喜。难道你听不懂什么叫惊喜？让你翻译翻译什么叫惊喜？惊喜翻译出来给我听！
Surprise! It's a surprise, no need to translate. Don't tell me you don't get what 'surprise' means. I'm telling you to translate 'surprise' for me! Translate 'surprise' and let me hear it!
什么他妈的叫惊喜？什么什么？
What the fuck is a 'surprise'? What the...?
他妈的，叫！他妈的！
Goddamn it! Shout! Goddamn it!
惊喜！什么他妈的叫惊喜啊！惊喜就是三天之后，我出180万给你们重生剿匪，先杀我的腿！
A surprise! What the hell is a surprise?! The surprise is that in three days, I'll put up 1.8 million for you guys to raid the bandits. But first, kill my legs!
明白了吗？这就是惊喜啊！
Get it? That's the surprise!
肥肥。
Fatty.
飞飞，惊喜就是三天之后，给你一百八十万两银子，出城剿匪，接上他的腿。
Feifei, the surprise is that in three days, I'll give you 1.8 million taels of silver to leave the city, fight the bandits, and get his leg back.
大哥，这特么是惊喜啊！小弟我愿意等你三天。
Big bro, this is a f*cking pleasant surprise! I'm willing to wait for you for three days.
黄老爷，康老爷是我的挚爱，你可不能夺我所爱啊！
Master Huang, Master Kang is my beloved. You can't take what I love from me!
要人，要人！
Help! Help!
这……
[Game sound]